(SIREN WAILING IN DISTANCE)
DRIVER: There's 100,000 streets in this city.
You don't need to know the route.
You give me a time and a place,
I give you a five-minute window.
Anything happens in that five minutes and I'm yours.
No matter what.
Anything happens a minute either side of that
and you're on your own.
Do you understand?
Good.
And you won't be able to
reach me on this phone again.
Hey, there you are!
She's down there.
Plain Jane Boring, just like you asked for,
but I dropped in 300 horses on the inside,
she is going to fly.
You look like a zombie, kid.
You getting any sleep?
Can I offer you some Benzedrine,
Dexedrine, caffeine, nicotine?
Oh, you don't smoke.
That's right.
Better off.
There she is!
Chevy Impala, the most popular car
in the State of California.
No one will be looking at you.
(SIREN WAILING)
(RADIO ANNOUNCER CALLING BASKETBALL GAME)
(GUNSHOT)
(ALARM SOUNDING)
(BEEPS)
(STATIC)
POLICE OFFICER 1: ...Robert Victor 3.
POLICE DISPATCH: License 5-1-4. Robert Victor 3...
(DISPATCH CONTINUES)
(TURNS UP VOLUME)
POLICE DISPATCH: Code 30 Ringer located at 421 South Alameda.
Reports of shots ﬁred at Code 30.
Come on.
Where the fuck is he? Come on.
(SIREN WAILING)
POLICE DISPATCH: Unit 5, what's your 20?
POLICE OFFICER 1: We are approximately two minutes from that location.
Come on, man. Where the hell are you?
Come on!
Come on! Get in! Get in! Get in!
Whew! Whew! Come on, man.
Go, go, go, go, go!
(TIRES SCREECHING)
POLICE DISPATCH: All units be advised.
Possible vehicle in question.
Late model silver Impala.
POLICE OFFICER 1: 1-Adam-3, South Bay at Seventh, clear.
Roger, 1-Adam-3
Requesting air unit support.
(DISPATCH CONTINUES)
POLICE OFFICER 2: Unit 5 to Dispatch, heading eastbound on Sixth.
POLICE DISPATCH: Copy that, Unit 5.
(HELICOPTER HOVERING)
POLICE DISPATCH: Base to Air 3.
Any sign of that silver Impala ?
AIR 3: Air 3 to Base. Negative.
Got a visual heading west on Seventh Street bridge.
(ENGINE REVVING)
Copy, Air 3. All units, be advised...
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Base, Air 3 here.
We've lost visual on suspect.
(HELICOPTER HOVERING)
Base to Air 3. Possible gang shooting in progress.
Proceed immediately to Washington and La Brea.
(SIRENS WAILING)
Roger, Dispatch. I'm out.
(RADIO STATIC)
POLICE DISPATCH: All westbound units, be advised.
Suspect last seen near Seventh Street and Santa Fe.
(RADIO ANNOUNCER CONTINUES CALLING GAME)
(TURNS UP VOLUME)
POLICE OFFICER 3: Dispatch, this is 1-Adam-6.
Possible suspect vehicle sighted at stoplight.
Stand by.
Roger, Unit 6.
(ACCELERATING)
(SIREN WAILING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(RADIO ANNOUNCER CALLS END OF BASKETBALL GAME)
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
(CROWD CLAMORING)
(SIRENS WAILING)
(WOMAN SCREAMS)
[ music ]
(NIGHTCALL PLAYING)
" I'm giving you a night call "
" To tell you how I feel "
" I want to drive you through the night "
" Down the hills "
" I'm gonna tell you something "
" You don't want to hear "
" I'm gonna show you where it's dark "
" But have no fear "
" There's something inside you "
" It's hard to explain "
" They're talking about you, boy "
" But you're still the same "
" There's something inside you "
" It's hard to explain "
" They're talking about you, boy "
" But you're still the same "
" There's something inside you "
" It's hard to explain "
" They're talking about you, boy "
" But you're still the same "
What floor? Fourth. Thanks.
Hey, kid, you know what?
Director wants to see a roll over.
Are you okay with that?
Remember, if you don't
feel good, just abort the shot.
There's no shame in that, all right?
I mean, you're...
You're doubling for the star.
You're not like a day player or anything.
And I got you 500 more, huh.
Of course, we split that.
You Okay? Ready to go?
All right. Counting on you!
PRODUCTION MANAGER: Excuse me, pal.
I just need a minute here.
Before I put you on camera,
I need you to sign this contract.
It just basically releases liability to the company
in case you die, get maimed, or seriously injured.
ASSISTANT DIRECTOR: And action!
(CAR SPEEDING)
ASSISTANT DIRECTOR: All right, that's a cut!
Oh, kid!
That was fantastic!
Just fantastic.
Okay. How you doing?
You all right?
You were good.
That was perfect.
IRENE: You're a monkey.
BENICIO: No, you're the monkey.
(Softly) You're the monkey.
You're the monkey.
No, you're the monkey.
Hey, tell me one thing.
BENICIO: I love you.
I love you.
(CAR ENGINE HISSING)
Ah!
Where should I put this?
In the kitchen.
Thank you.
Just be a second.
Scary.
(BENICIO LAUGHS)
Hey, you want a toothpick?
IRENE: You want a glass of water?
Okay.
(POURING WATER)
Thanks.
So, you just moved to LA?
No, I've been here for a while.
You're just new here?
Mmm-hmm.
That's Benicio's father.
Where is he?
He's in prison.
Oh.
What do you do?
I drive.
Like a limo driver?
No, like, for movies.
Oh.
You mean, all the car chases and stuff?
Yeah.
Is that dangerous?
It's only part-time.
Mostly I work at a garage.
Where?
Reseda Boulevard.
I gotta go.
Okay.
Thanks for the water.
Say bye. BENICIO: Bye.
(SIGHS)
WAITER: Mr. Rose, your food, sir.
ROSE: Okay.
Chicken chow mein and some Peking duck.
Okay. Where are the chopsticks?
WAITER: Oh, you know the guy just...
(WAITER MUMBLING) Go get them.
Go get them.
I don't want that.
You eat it.
Chopsticks and a fortune cookie.
Put out the fucking cigarette.
I'm eating.
Sorry.
What's the matter with you?
I'm just...
What happened to all the ashtrays in this town?
(CHUCKLING)
You run a perfectly good business.
I don't know why
you want to change now.
You know how much
my business made last year?
Thirty grand.
I can build a car in six months
and in six seconds, these jerks
write it off as a stunt
that won't even make
it into the movie.
Mmm-hmm.
See, all I need is
a hard used stock car.
That's all.
And I figure we start off with
small town circuit and we work our way up.
And once we get to the show,
we're talking millions.
WAITER: I have the chopsticks, sir. Yeah.
Where's the cookies?
WAITER: Uh... You know,
I... Forget it. Forget it.
So, you still haven't
given me a number.
All right.
$430,000.
(EXCLAIMS)
Mr. Rose, I wouldn't come to you with this
unless I was absolutely sure about it.
How can you be sure, Shannon?
What do you got that the
big professional race teams don't?
I got the driver.
You just told me
they had half a dozen drivers.
Not like this one.
This kid is special.
I've been working
with him for a while.
I've never seen anything like it.
If I had the money,
I'd back him myself.
Yeah, but you don't have the money.
Mr. Rose, you put
this kid behind the wheel,
there's nothing he can't do.
There's money here.
You can't lose.
Fuck, you eating chink food
in my fucking restaurant?
What's a Jew doing running a pizzeria?
You remember Shannon.
Take a fucking hike.
I want to talk to my partner.
I'm just fucking with you.
How you doing, Shannon?
How's the fucking leg?
I paid my debt.
I'll think about it.
Okay?
But I want to meet the kid first.
That's all I ask.
(ENGINE REVVING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Come on, I want you to meet somebody.
And whatever you do like
about the car, don't say anything.
I want to drive the price down a little bit.
Kid, I want you to meet Mr. Bernie Rose.
Nice to meet you.
My hands are a little dirty.
So are mine.
(CHUCKLES)
Good driving out there.
Thanks.
SHANNON: He's a good kid.
So, what do you think?
Do we get the 400?
I'll give you 300 for 70%.
Done.
Right. Good.
(LAUGHING) You won't be sorry.
I'm Shannon.
- Hi. Irene.
Irene. How can I help you?
It just broke down.
Just broke down. Just like that.
IRENE: Mmm-hmm.
You want me to take a look at it?
IRENE: Yes, please.
All right. Uh...
We got all our bays full.
Hey, pal, just drop it down here.
We'll push it in, all right?
We want to push her into number three.
The car, not you.
Oh, good. (LAUGHS)
Hi.
- Hi.
You two know each other?
Don't.
Oh. Look at that.
We're neighbors.
Neighbors?
Very good. Mmm-hmm.
Well, we'll try to be neighborly too.
You blinked.
What?
Can I call a cab from here?
Yeah. Sure.
What am I talking about?
You and the kid are neighbors, right?
He can take you home.
Oh, no.
I'd feel bad.
No, no.
Don't even think twice about it.
He'd be happy to do it.
He's a good guy.
You know, he walked into my
shop here about five or six years ago.
Right out of the blue.
Asking for a job.
So I put him to the test to
see what he could do.
The kid's amazing.
Yeah.
So, I hire him on the spot.
Boom. (SNAPS FINGERS)
At about half the wages I
normally pay. (LAUGHS)
He didn't blink an eye.
Hey, kid, come over here
for a second, will you?
And I have been
exploiting him ever since.
(LAUGHING)
(SHUSHING) Don't tell him.
Looks like we have a bigger
problem than I thought.
And we're going to have to keep
the car here for a few days.
So I offered your services
to take Benicio and Irene home.
That be okay?
Yeah, sure. Yeah.
I don't have wheels on my car.
(LAUGHING) Okay.
It's one thing you should know about me.
Well, put the tires on.
You got five minutes? Yeah.
Hey, do you want to see something?
Yeah.
Okay.
[ music ]
(A REAL HERO PLAYING)
" Back against the wall and odds "
" With the strength of a will and a cause "
" Your pursuits are called outstanding "
" You're emotionally complex "
" Against the grain of dystopic claims "
" On the thoughts your actions entertained "
" And you have proved to be "
" A real human being "
" And a real hero "
" Real human being "
" A pilot on a cold, cold morn` "
" One-hundred fifty-five people on board "
" All safe and all rescued "
" From the slowly sinking ship "
" Water warmer than his head so cool "
" In that tight bind knew what to do "
" And you have proved to be "
" A real human being "
" Real human being "
That was good.
He had a good time.
Me, too.
Sorry if I put you on
the spot showing up like that.
It's okay.
I'm not doing anything this weekend.
If you want a ride or something.
(BENICIO LAUGHING)
SHANNON: Don't worry about her
bumps and bruises, that's just fiberglass.
That's easily replaceable.
Put a coat of paint on there,
some sponsor decals.
Look at the tread on the tire,
it's still good, huh?
We're in business.
We paid 300 fucking grand
for this piece of shit?
ROSE: I paid for it.
Out of my own pocket.
This is just the shell.
It's the inside that counts,
not the outside.
Right, Shannon?
SHANNON: You are correct, sir.
Fuck that shit. I pay 300 for something,
I want everybody to fucking see it.
ROSE: Of course you do.
Now, this.
That is one motherfucking fine-ass
pussy mobile, motherfucker.
Damn!
Shannon, sell him the car.
He wouldn't be able to find
pussy in a whorehouse.
SHANNON: You know what?
This car will even
make you good-looking.
NINO: I'm already good-looking, pal.
How's it going?
When's our first race?
Uh, pretty soon.
You gonna be ready?
I hope so.
(LAUGHING) " I hope so."
Hey, no false modesty.
I got a lot of money in this.
Did Shannon ever tell you how we met?
No.
I used to produce movies.
In the '80s.
Kind of like action films. Sexy stuff.
One critic called them European.
I thought they were shit.
Anyway, he arranged all the cars for me.
Did all the stunts.
I liked him.
I liked having him around.
Even though he overcharged
the shit out of me.
His next business venture,
he got involved with
some of Nino's friends.
They didn't go for the overcharging bit.
They broke his pelvis.
He's never had a lot of luck.
The reason I'm telling you this
is, .. that he has alot invested in you.
And so do I.
So anything you need, you call me.
We're a team now.
(LAUGHS) I'm excited.
Nino, let's get the fuck out of here.
(TV PLAYING)
Is he a bad guy?
Yeah.
How can you tell?
Because he's a shark.
There's no good sharks?
No. I mean, just look at him.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Does he look like a good guy to you?
Hi. How are you?
Good. How are you? Good.
This is Cindy.
Hi.
(PHONE RINGING)
That was my husband's lawyer.
He's coming home in a week.
[ music ]
(UNDER YOUR SPELL PLAYING IN ANOTHER APARTMENT)
" I don't eat "
" I don't sleep "
" I do nothing but think of you "
" I don't eat "
" I don't sleep "
" I do nothing but think of you "
" You keep me under your spell "
We're here celebrating, but
it's a shameful thing what I did.
And I have a lot of making up
to do to everyone.
But second chances are rare.
Right?
And that's worth celebrating. Right?
So I want to make a toast
to that lady right there.
Thanks for staying.
I love you, Renie.
Salud.
" I don't sleep "
" I do nothing but think of you "
" I don't eat "
" I don't sleep "
" I do nothing but think of you "
" You keep me under your spell "
(VOCALIZING)
(DOOR CLOSES)
Hey.
Hi.
Sorry about the noise.
I was going to call the cops.
I wish you would.
STANDARD: Oi! You're getting heavier.
STANDARD: Hey.
IRENE: Hey.
(COUPLE SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
STANDARD: Hey.
How you doing?
Hi. This guy's been telling me a lot about you.
Says you been coming around, helping out a lot.
Yeah?
Helping out?
Is that right?
Is that right? Mmm-hmm.
Oh.
That's very nice.
That's nice of you. Thank you.
You're welcome.
You drive for the movies?
Yeah.
I can take that.
No, no, no. I got it.
Let Mommy talk to her friend.
Come on.
Have a good night.
You're Shannon's buddy, right?
We met last year.
You drove me and my brother
back from Palm Springs.
(MUMBLES)
We hired another wheelman.
I spent six months in jail.
My brother, he got himself killed.
I got this sweet job coming up.
How about this?
You shut your mouth.
Or I'll kick your teeth down your
throat and I'll shut it for you.
Nice seeing you again.
STANDARD: Come on, it's okay.
Come here.
Don't be scared.
Don't tell Mommy, okay?
Okay?
It's a secret between the boys.
Oh, fuck me.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(TV PLAYING)
Who were they?
(LAUGHS) What the fuck are you going to do?
You're gonna go beat them up for me?
Huh, stunt guy?
Why the fuck do you want
to know who they are?
Huh?
(SIGHS)
There are some guys that want
me to do a job for them
and I'm not going to do it.
That's who they are.
What's the job?
They want me to rob
a pawnshop in the Valley.
Why?
'Cause I owe them some protection money
from when I was inside.
It's 2,000 bucks.
But as soon as I got out,
... oh, it's 5,000 bucks.
Oh, no, actually, it's $10,000. $20,000.
Tomorrow I don't know what
the fuck it's going to be.
What are you going to do?
That's a really good question.
They said they were going to
come after Benicio and Irene next.
You okay?
You want something to drink?
What is it you got there?
Can I see?
One of those men gave you that?
Mmm-hmm.
They told me not to lose it.
You want me to keep that for you?
Okay.
(SIGHS)
How's Benice?
Good.
You just saying that?
No.
What do you mean?
I saw that Standard was in an accident.
Yeah.
What happened?
He got beat up.
Mmm-hmm.
Why?
Just drunk kids.
You should come over.
You should come and see him.
You want to...
You want to hear a story?
Do you want to hear how
Mommy and me met? Yeah.
Yeah? Okay.
(IRENE CHUCKLING)
STANDARD: We were at a party.
And she was 19 years old.
IRENE: Seventeen.
You weren't 17.
I was.
Wow. So it was illegal?
IRENE: Yeah.
(BOTH CHUCKLING)
(LAUGHING) All right.
So I illegally walked over
to a 17-year-old girl.
And I walk up and I say, "Hello, Miss.
"What is your name?"
And she didn't say anything.
And then I said...
"Well, my name is Standard Gabriel."
Then what did you say?
I said...
"Where is the deluxe version?" (LAUGHS)
(STANDARD LAUGHS)
STANDARD: She's good, man.
Sharp.
Oh, man. It killed me.
(LAUGHS)
And then a year later, you popped out, man.
It was the best day of my life.
(STARTS ENGINE)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
DRIVER: If I drive for you, you get your money.
You tell me where we start, where we're going,
where we're going afterwards.
I give you five minutes when we get there.
Anything happens in that five minutes, and I'm yours.
No matter what.
Anything a minute on either side of that and you're on your own.
I don't sit in while you're running it down.
I don't carry a gun.
I drive.
You look like you're hard to work with.
Not if we understand each other.
What's to understand?
I can't do this thing alone.
COOK: You got Blanche.
Come on, man.
COOK: (LAUGHING) She's beautiful. Look at her.
What the fuck you rolling your eyes at for?
You know what, get the fuck out of here.
Get Up!
Standard, take her with you
and go get her a fucking coke!
Okay, here's the deal.
This much for Blanche,
this much for that asshole, minus
what he owes me,
and this much for you.
You still interested?
Good. Anything else?
When you get your money, his debt's paid.
He's out for good.
And you never go near his family again.
You understand?
STANDARD: I'm here with my family.
And my new friend.
And...
Toast to the future.
To our future.
Hey.
I'll see you in five minutes.
I'll see you in four.
(WATCH TICKING)
(GUNSHOT) (BLANCHE GASPS)
BLANCHE: Oh, my...
(GUNSHOTS CONTINUE)
Shit!
Oh, my God!
(CAR HONKING)
(EXCLAIMING)
(HONKING)
(TV NEWS IN BACKGROUND)
How much did Cook say
we were going to get?
Forty grand.
Stay here.
(DIALING PHONE)
(CHATTER ON POLICE RADIO)
POLICEWOMAN: When was the last time you saw your husband?
Can you answer the question?
Ma'am.
(PHONE RINGING)
BENICIO ON PHONE: Hello?
Benicio? ls that you?
Yeah.
HEY.
Is your mother there?
Uh, huh. She's sitting down
talking to the police.
Okay, just tell her I'm going to
call her back, okay?
Okay, We-
In related news, an attempted
robbery turned tragic today
when the owner of a local pawnshop
opened fire on an intruder.
The armed robber was
pronounced dead at the scene.
He has been identiﬁed as
Standard Gabriel of Echo Park, Los Angeles.
Other details are unclear, but
the owner of the pawnshop
told reporters that Gabriel acted alone
and that no money had been stolen.
In other news, four
high school athletes were arrested...
If he saw you take the money
and he saw you get in the car,
then why didn't he say anything?
I have no idea.
Did you have any idea
there'd be a second car?
I already told you everything.
(MUFFLED SOBBING)
Now, you just got
a little boy's father killed.
And you almost got us killed.
And now you're lying to me.
So, how about this?
From now on, every word
out of your mouth is the truth.
(CRYING)
Or I'm going to hurt you.
Do you understand?
Now what did Cook tell you?
He said there'd be another car to hold us up
but he didn't say anything about all this money.
He didn't say anything about anyone getting killed.
You were going to rip us off?
What's his real name?
He says it's Chris, but I just call him Cook.
You're going to take me to him right now.
(BLANCHE WHIMPERS)
Do you understand?
Yes.
(PHONE VIBRATING)
(DOORKNOB RATTLING)
(BANGING ON DOOR)
(FOOTSTEPS)
(GRUNTS)
(THUD)
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
(CONTINUES RINGING)
Easy. Easy.
What did you do with the cash?
'Cause I could keep it safe for you...
Will you just stop it?
This guy Cook, does he have a real name?
Chris.
Maybe.
I'll ask Bernie.
See if he knows him.
Jesus, I can't...
I can't stop thinking about what
we could do with all that dough.
Will you just stop?
All right.
A lot of guys mess around with married women,
but you're the only one I know,
who robs a joint ...
just to pay back the husband.
Crazy.
Don't worry about it.
I'll take care of it.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
Where's Cook?
He's in the dressing room.
Where's that?
It's over there.
(SCREAMING)
(PANTING)
Whose money do I have?
Don't worry.
They're going to come get it.
No! No!
Call them.
Somebody call Nino!
Do you remember this?
(COOK CHOKING)
(PHONE RINGING)
MAN: Hello.
Nino?
No, sorry, pal.
Why don't you call back later?
We're closed.
I could, but I think Nino would be
upset that you made him wait.
Can I ask what this is about?
I have something of his.
And that would be?
A million dollars.
Please hold.
NINO: You got something
that fucking belongs to me?
It seems that way.
And you're calling me?
Why?
You expect me to buy
my own shit back from you?
I'm not selling it.
I'm going to give you a time and a place
and you're going to come and get it.
Do you understand?
And what do you get out of it?
Just that.
Out of it.
And your partners are happy with that?
I don't have any partners.
You discuss this with anybody else?
No, just you.
You're not very good at this, are you?
(DRIVER HANGS UP)
Go check out who this fucking guy is.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
(IRENE EXHALING)
Can I talk to you for a minute?
Can't talk.
I have to go.
Can I just walk with you for a..
Yeah.
I have to tell you something.
Standard was into some...
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
...guys in prison for a lot of money.
And they were going to hurt you
and Benicio if he didn't pay it.
He asked me for my help.
Everything went wrong.
I'm sorry.
I still got the money.
You can have it if you wanted to.
You can take Benicio...
I just thought you could get
out of here if you wanted.
I could come with you.
I could look out for you.
(ELEVATOR DOOR OPENS)
Sorry. Wrong floor.
(GRUNTING)
They came to my apartment, Shannon.
How'd they know where I live?
I told you. I was going to call Bernie.
I just wanted him to know that...
That it wasn't about...
That you're not interested in the money.
That you just did it for the girl.
(GASPS)
I just... Why did you have to
fucking tell them about Irene?
Calm down!
You told them about Irene!
Calm down, kid.
Just calm down.
I should fucking kill you!
You told them about Irene.
I just wanted him to know
that as soon as you returned the money,
that was the end of it.
That's all. I didn't know...
How was I supposed to know?
How was I supposed to know that? Okay?
Look, let me just talk to Bernie. Okay.
Why you got to fuck everything up, Shannon?
How was I supposed to know
everything led to Nino?
They're gonna come looking for me.
And they're going to come for you.
Do you understand?
You got to get out of here.
And you got to get out now.
Listen to me. Oh, God.
Listen to me, Shannon.
Listen.
You get out of here and
you never fucking come back.
You never come back.
What are you going to do?
I already gave you my advice.
You should have taken the money
and left the guy alone.
It's not that simple, Bernie.
No, of course not.
Now that it's bounced up in your face.
COOK: Nino, I owe you this guy.
Just give me a little time and I'll get rid of him.
Shut the fuck up,
you fucking monkey.
The money belongs to some
half-assed wise guy out of Philly.
Now, I got tipped off,
he was stashing a million bucks in a pawnshop.
He was going to invest it here in LA.
He was going to set up a rival operation.
So you stole from the East Coast mob?
No. I stole from some jumped-up punk,
who was trying to step on our action.
Yeah? Then why didn't you come to me,
before you set up this dummy robbery?
Before you hire this piece of shit.
This is something off to the side, Bernie.
I didn't want to involve you in this.
Well, I'm involved now!
I'm going to tell you something.
Anybody ...
Anybody finds out you stole from the family,
we're both dead.
What fucking family?
The family who still calls me a fucking kike!
To my face!
Yeah, I'm 59 years old, Bernie.
They still pinch my cheek
like I'm some fucking kid.
Family.
The money always flows up, Izzy.
You know that.
(NINO SIGHS)
That's why this driver's gotta go, Bernie.
He's gotta go.
And your pal, Shannon.
These are the only two guys
who can tie me to this robbery.
(COOK SCREAMING)
(GRUNTING)
Now it's your turn to clean up after me.
All these priceless cars.
One would think you'd have better locks.
Why?
Door's always open to you.
Going somewhere?
Uh... (LAUGHS)
Thinking about it.
I'm looking for your driver.
You break in here, I figure it's bad news.
No, Shannon.
It's bad luck.
2,000 heists a year in this city,
he has to pick the wrong one.
He tried to put it right.
Well, he picked the wrong guy for that, too.
My partner is a belligerent asshole
with his back against the wall.
Right now, so am I.
If I don't set this straight, I'm in big trouble.
Any idea where he might be?
Mexico.
Or maybe it was Belize.
Really?
I was getting excited about this whole thing.
My name on a car!
I mean, look how beautiful.
I wanted to see my name on this thing.
I think we would have made a
go at this business.
(GASPS) Don't worry.
Don't worry. That's it.
It's done.
There's no pain.
It's over. It's over.
(GASPING)
(SIGHING)
[ music ]
(OH, MY LOVE PLAYING)
" Oh, my love "
" Look and see "
" The sun rising from the river "
" Nature's miracle once more "
" Will light the world "
" But this light "
" Is not for those men "
" Still lost in "
" An old black shadow "
" Won't you help me to believe "
" That they will see "
" A day "
" A brighter day "
" When all the shadows "
" Will fade away "
" That day I'll cry "
" That I believe "
" Oh, my love "
" High above us "
" The sun now "
" Embraces nature "
" And from nature we should learn "
" That all can start again "
" As the stars must fade away "
" To give a bright new day "
What the fuck was that?
(DOOR CLOSES)
Let's get out of here.
Yeah.
(PANTING)
ROSE: Hello?
DRIVER: You know the story
about the scorpion and the frog?
Your friend Nino didn't make it across the river.
I think this has gone on long enough.
You see any reason for it to continue?
What do you say we meet?
Why?
Well, you, me, and your girlfriend
are the only players left.
How's that for a reason?
When?
Tomorrow.
There's a place on Sherman Way,
it's a restaurant called The Great Wall.
Do you know it?
DRIVER: Can I talk to you?
I won't keep you long.
I have to go somewhere and
I don't think I can come back.
But I just want you to know.
Getting to be around you and Benicio
was the best thing that ever happened to me.
Did you bring the money?
Here's what I'm prepared to offer.
You give me the money, the girl is safe.
Forever.
Nobody knows about her.
She's off the map.
I can't offer you the same.
So, this is what I would suggest.
We conclude our deal.
We'll shake hands.
You start the rest of your life.
Any dreams you have, or plans,
or hopes for your future...
I think you're going to
have to put that on hold.
For the rest of your life you're going to
be looking over your shoulder.
I'm just telling you this
because I want you to know the truth.
But the girl is safe.
Where's the money now?
It's in the car.
Come on.
(YELLS)
(GRUNTS)
[ music ]
(A REAL HERO PLAYING)
" A pilot on a cold, cold morn` "
" One-hundred fifty-five people on board "
" All safe and all rescued "
" From the slowly sinking ship "
" Water warmer than his head so cool "
" In that tight bind knew what to do "
" And you have proved to be "
" A real human being "
" And a real hero "
" Real human being "